<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jocadbz's Personal Site</title><link>https://jocadbz.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on Jocadbz's Personal Site</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© Jocadbz</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:38:38 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jocadbz.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://jocadbz.xyz/resume/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:38:38 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://jocadbz.xyz/resume/</guid><description>(Also available in PDF)
Joaquim Madureira Systems Administrator Highly skilled and dynamic Network Systems Analyst, bringing forth the ability to effectively manage and oversee optimal network services for organizations. Adept in setting up administrator and server accounts, and experienced in managing the functionality of systems. Resourceful, and committed to continually advancing my knowledge of relevant technologies. Adept in carefully diagnosing and assessing issues, and offering real viable solutions.
PERSONAL INFORMATION Address: Brazil Nationality: Brazillian SOCIAL PROFILES LinkedIn: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Discord Bot</title><link>https://jocadbz.xyz/post/creating-a-discord-bot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:31:09 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://jocadbz.xyz/post/creating-a-discord-bot/</guid><description>&lt;p>My hilarious journey at creating a discord bot&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://jocadbz.xyz/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:15:16 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://jocadbz.xyz/about/</guid><description>About me Oh&amp;hellip; You Actually want to know something about me? Jeez&amp;hellip; Fine.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently 17 years old. (TODO: Update this page next year)
I&amp;rsquo;m still in highschool, and I&amp;rsquo;m also working as a software developer for an undisclosed OSS project.
I grew interest in computers at a young age. I still vividly remmeber booting up my enourmous 2001 notebook to play Trackmania united in my childhood. Fun times. I also used to game a lot, and since gaming in 2012 with a Wii was hard, I had to get my way around most of the problems I had.</description></item></channel></rss>